> > 布莱恩: 我们要做一个新的文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian: We're gonna make a new file.
实际上，让我们做一个全新的目录而不是源。
Actually, let's just make a whole
new directory instead of source.
它会被称为还原器，或者仅仅是还原器。
And it's gonna be called reducers.,
or just reducers, rather.
在简化程序中，我们将有一个名为 index.js。
Inside of reducers,
we're gonna have one called index.js.
这将是根减速器
This is gonna be the root reducer.
所以我们要说进口
So we're gonna say import.
combineReducer， combineReducers from 'redux'。
combineReducers, combineReducers
from 'redux'.
这只是写根减速器的小帮手方法
This is just a little helper method
that makes writing the root reducer
然后我们就会再去一个叫进口的地方
a little bit easier, and then we're gonna
make another one called import location.
我们还没做的地方减压器
The location reducer from ./location
which we haven't made yet, but
我们就能在这里做个第二次了
we'll make here in just a second.
我想说出口默认的组合减速器
And I want to say export
default combineReducers and
为其提供位置选项 : 位置。
give it an option of location: location.
> > 布莱恩: 但因为这两者都是一样的
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
because these two are the same things,
我们可以把它们组合成一件事对吧
we can actually just combine
them into one thing, right?
所以，如果我这样说，我们其实可以做到这一点。
So if I say that,
we can actually just do that.
>> 布莱恩: 那么组合减速器会做什么，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what combineReducers does,
你可以把 Redux 商店想象成一个大对象，对吧 ?
you can think of a Redux store
as a really big object, right?
它应该是一个数据树。
It's supposed to be a tree of data.
所以我们要在这里跟踪我们的位置
So we're gonna keep track of our
location here, do I still have.
这个是吧
This one, right?
我们会在 Redux 内部追踪这个位置
We're gonna keep track of this location
inside of Redux instead of being inside of
雷法对吧
React, right?
所以我们只能让这个位置减速
So we're gonna make this
location reducer only
影响此位置参数或状态树。
affect this location parameter or
piece of the state tree.
所以我们说任何时间地点都被修改了
So we're saying any time that
the location gets modified,
基本上是这样做的
run this reducer, basically.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
太酷了
Cool.
我们再做一个叫做 location.js的文件，
So let's go make another file
here called location.js,
在这个减速器的目录里
inside of this Reducer's's directory.
这将会是一个简单的减压器
And this is gonna be a really simple
reducer, it's gonna be export
缺省功能位置，您将为其提供缺省状态。
default function location,
you're gonna give it a default state.
州 = ，不管你想要什么，西雅图，华盛顿
The state = and make it whatever you want,
Seattle, Washington or
旧金山加利福尼亚
San Francisco, California.
而且这也要采取行动
And that's gonna take
in an action as well.
所以如果你以前没见过这个
So if you've never seen
this in a parameter before,
它说，嘿，如果我得到国家的支持，
it's saying, hey, if I get state,
那就用这个，如果我不处于任何状态，那么默认状态是这个，对吗 ?
then use that, if I don't get any state
then default state is this, right?
只是让它更容易些
Just makes that a little bit easier.
> > 布莱恩: 然后我就会说
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then I'm just gonna say if
(action.type ===
"CHANGE_LOCATION") 返回 action.payload。
'CHANGE_LOCATION') return action.payload.
>> Brian: Else 返回状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Else return state.
>> Brian: 现在，我们也可以将此转换为 switch 语句。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now, we can turn this
into a switch statement as well.
我觉得在我的笔记里我是这么做的
I think actually in my notes,
I do it that way, but
它基本上就是一个 if 语句
it's basically just an if statement.
>> 布莱恩: 那么，什么是行动?
&gt;&gt; Brian: So, what is action?
行动将成为我的目标
Action is gonna be an object that I get
把行动分派给雷德克斯
from whatever is dispatching
the action to redux.
所以我说，嘿， redux ，只在这个减速器里回应
So I'm saying, hey, redux,
only respond in this reducer
如果操作类型等于 CHANGE_LOCATION，那么是吗 ?
if the action type equals CHANGE_LOCATION,
right?
要不什么都不做就把对象传过去吧
Otherwise don't do anything,
just pass the object on, right?
所以在这个特殊情况下，如果我有一个动作类型的 CHANGE_ANIMAL，
So in this particular case,
if I got an action type of CHANGE_ANIMAL,
它会忽略它对吧
it would just ignore it, right?
但在这个特定的情况下，它说，如果是 CHANGE_LOCATION，
But in this particular case it's saying,
if this is CHANGE_LOCATION,
然后我想让你把它更新为有效载荷
then I want you to update it
to be whatever the payload is.
如果现在是加利福尼亚州旧金山，那就更新它。
If it's now San Francisco, California,
then update it to be that.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
现在，我们在这里有了这个功能，这个减速器，这个是非常稳定的，对吧 ?
Now, we have this function here, this
reducer, and this is so testable, right?
我可以用不同的方法测试这一百万种方法。
I can test this a million different ways.
好，如果这个国家是这个的话，如果这个国家是这个国家是空的，
Okay, if the state is this, if the state
is that, if the state is empty,
如果状态为空，那么状态为数字，对吗 ?
if the state is null,
if the state is numbers, right?
你可以说鉴于这个国家和这个行动
And you can say,
given this state and this action,
我应该把这东西弄回来的对吧
I should always get this thing back,
right?
那就是计算机科学术语
It's which is the computer
science term that means
我可以用同样的参数运行这 1001 次
I can run this 1,001 times
with the same parameters,
而在第一次的时候它会以同样的方式运作
and on the 1,001st time,
it's gonna work exactly the same way.
现在，如果我在做这样的事情，让 x = 0，
Now, if I was doing something
like this where I had let x = 0,
然后说 X++ x ，对吧 ?
and then I was saying x++ and + x, right?
我不知道这很好笑
I didn't know this was, that's funny.
把它们放在一起
It puts those together.
这是个问题对吧
This is a problem, right?
这不再是纯粹的功能。
This is no longer a pure function.
这有副作用，这不再是对吧 ?
This has side effects,
this is no longer right?
如果我把这个叫做 1001 次，在 1002 的时候是什么呢 ?
If I call this a 1001 times,
on the 1002nd time what's it gonna be?
答案是不一样的对吧
Something different is the answer, right?
不管它是什么都不重要
It doesn't matter actually what it is.
在一千二零零的时候就不一样了。
It's just not the same
on the 1,002nd time.
所以别这么做
So don't do this.
这些应该是纯函数，您可以根据需要多次运行这些函数，
These should be pure functions that you
can run them as many times as you want,
周围的环境都没有改变
and nothing ambient is changing about it.
>> Brian: 它必须具有缺省状态，因此请确保您这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian: It must have a default state,
so make sure you do that.
另一件事就是行动类型不是你付的钱
And the other thing here is if the action
type is not the one that you're paying
请注意确保您刚刚恢复状态，对吗 ?
attention to make sure that you
just return the state, right?
因为它假定您总是要返回某种状态。
Because it assumes that you're always
going to return a state of some sort.
这是非常关键的事情。
That's a very key thing here.
所以如果我没有这一部分
So if I didn't have this part and
我有一些我不认识的行动对吧
I had some action that I didn't recognize,
right?
因此，如果这是 CHANGE_ANIMAL ，那么新的状态将是未定义的，对吗 ?
So if this was CHANGE_ANIMAL,
the new state would be undefined, right?
这可能不是你想要的
Which is probably not what you want.
请注意，我在此处使用 action.payload 和 action.type。
Notice I'm using action.payload here,
and action.type.
你的行动唯一需要的就是一种类型，那是很困难的要求，
The only thing that your action has to
have is a type, that's hard requirement,
一定有类型好吗
must have a type, okay?
你说的有效载荷是你的
What you call the payload is up to you.
我选择遵守一个叫流量标准行动的东西
I'm choosing to adhere to something
called a flux standard action.
> > 布莱恩: 我没有真正的理由要这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian: There's no real
reason I have to do this.
只是安德鲁的光，谁是 ACD 的光。
It's just Andrew light,
who's or Andrew ACD light.
克拉克 - 安德鲁是他的名字，在 Facebook 上工作。
Clark Andrew, Clark is his name,
works at Facebook and
他是 Redux公司的联合创始人之一
one of the co-creators of Redux.
他说这就是行动应该是什么样的，
Made this and he just described that
this is what actions should look like,
类型，有效内容，错误和元。
types, payloads, error, and meta.
这是他们唯一能拥有的东西，对。
That's the only thing that they can have,
right.
所有其他东西都应该直接进入有效载荷
Everything else should just
go into payload basically.
你不必遵守这些
You don't have to adhere to that.
但我只是没有更好的主意
But I just don't have a better idea.
所以我选择遵守它
So I just choose to adhere to it.
> > 布莱恩: 好的
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, good.
我们要再做一个减压器
We're gonna make one more reducer for
主题我想说 theme.js
theme, I wanna say theme.js.
我们可以复制并粘贴这些信息。
We can actually just copy and paste this.
看起来就差不多了
It's gonna look almost the same.
对初始状态来说这将会是深蓝色的
So this is gonna be darkblue for
the initial state, and this is gonna be
CHANGE_THEME 和此函数的名称将成为主题。
CHANGE_THEME, and the name of this
function is going to be theme.
> > 布莱恩: 现在，我知道你可能坐在那里想一些事情，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now, I know you're probably
sitting there thinking things like,
我能把它变成抽象的还原剂发生器吗
could I make this into some,
like, abstract reducer generator?
你可以，还有图书馆能帮你。
You can, and there are libraries
that will help you with that.
但是现在，让我们明确地说，对吧 ?
But for now,
let's just be explicit, right?
>> 布莱恩: 我是粉丝，你听说过干代码，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: I'm of the fan,
have you heard the term dry code, right?
不要重复自己
Do not repeat yourself.
我是个很喜欢湿码的人写了三遍
I'm very much a fan of wet code,
write everything three times.
第四次之后，再把它改写成某种东西，对吧 ?
And then after the fourth time,
then rewrite it into some thing, right?
因为过早的优化会杀死项目，对吧 ?
Because premature optimization
kills projects, right?
你写了几遍抽象的东西，对吧 ?
How many times have you written
something abstract, right?
然后就不会用它的抽象部分了，现在就很难用了，对吧 ?
And then never use the abstract part of it
and now it's just difficult to use, right?
这种情况经常发生在我
That frequently happens to me.
顺便说下我没说过这个
I didn't make that up, by the way,
someone else made that up.
好吧我要说进口主题
Okay, so I'm gonna say import theme
来自 ./theme and theme here.
from ./theme and theme here.